questions = [
  { question: 'What is the name of the pokemon I gave you?', answer1: 'Pink Panther', answer2: 'Jigglypuff', answer3: 'Bulbasaur', answer4: 'Wigglytuff', correct: '2', gif: 'https://giphy.com/embed/LoQSLWUbdmjp64zXYA'},
  { question: 'Where did we have our first kiss?', answer1: 'We never kissed', answer2: 'Your apartment', answer3: 'The Office', answer4: 'Hafenbar', correct: '4', gif: 'https://giphy.com/embed/CAguOaURcjHjO'},
  { question: 'What are the colors of my eyes?', answer1: 'Green', answer2: 'Brown', answer3: 'Purple', answer4: 'Blue', correct: '4', gif: 'https://giphy.com/embed/ffzhLUixCtlsc'},
  { question: 'Where to poke to make the other say "I miss you?"', answer1: 'The Heart', answer2: 'The Forehead', answer3: 'The Knee', answer4: 'The Nose', correct: '1', gif: 'https://giphy.com/embed/0kLGaWpOhn19MpH7by'},
  { question: 'Where did we go on our first date?', answer1: 'The Diner', answer2: 'The Billard Place', answer3: 'The Sushi Place', answer4: 'Dark Matter', correct: '3', gif: 'https://giphy.com/embed/XvZ8PJ4DSqzSM'},
  { question: 'What comes after 3?', answer1: '4', answer2: 'Banana', answer3: 'Pi', answer4: 'Tea', correct: '3', gif: 'https://giphy.com/embed/4JVTF9zR9BicshFAb7'},
  { question: 'When is my birthday?', answer1: '13th of April', answer2: '14th of March', answer3: '11th of April', answer4: '12th of March', correct: '1', gif: 'https://giphy.com/embed/3o7WIzRtKsA93IDauI'},
  { question: 'What is the best use of an Umbrella?', answer1: 'To keep away rain', answer2: 'To use as a lightsaber', answer3: 'To fly around', answer4: 'Umbrellas are not real', correct: '2', gif: 'https://giphy.com/embed/8hhfYrbc0XugC1XIeO'},
  { question: 'What is the key to our amazing relationship?', answer1: 'Snacks', answer2: 'Healthy Lifestyle', answer3: 'Boardgames', answer4: 'Communication', correct: '4', gif: 'https://giphy.com/embed/5vYwHanb6y3HWBQIox'},
  { question: 'Will you be my valentine?', answer1: 'Yes', answer2: 'Yes', answer3: 'Yes', answer4: 'Yes', correct: 'all', gif: 'https://giphy.com/embed/gMZwfxiCMoDgWvym8Y'},
];
